
export const panelModes = [
  {
    id: '1',
    question: 'fretboard',
    answer: 'name',
    __typename: 'PanelMode',
  },
  {
    id: '2',
    question: 'fretboard',
    answer: 'staff',
    __typename: 'PanelMode',
  },
  {
    id: '3',
    question: 'fretboard',
    answer: 'sound',
    __typename: 'PanelMode',
  },
  {
    id: '4',
    question: 'name',
    answer: 'fretboard',
    __typename: 'PanelMode',
  },
  {
    id: '5',
    question: 'name',
    answer: 'staff',
    __typename: 'PanelMode',
  },
  {
    id: '6',
    question: 'name',
    answer: 'sound',
    __typename: 'PanelMode',
  },
  {
    id: '7',
    question: 'staff',
    answer: 'fretboard',
    __typename: 'PanelMode',
  },
  {
    id: '8',
    question: 'staff',
    answer: 'name',
    __typename: 'PanelMode',
  },
  {
    id: '9',
    question: 'staff',
    answer: 'sound',
    __typename: 'PanelMode',
  },
  {
    id: '10',
    question: 'sound',
    answer: 'fretboard',
    __typename: 'PanelMode',
  },
  {
    id: '11',
    question: 'sound',
    answer: 'name',
    __typename: 'PanelMode',
  },
  {
    id: '12',
    question: 'sound',
    answer: 'staff',
    __typename: 'PanelMode',
  },
]

export const panel1 = {
  id: '1',
  question: 'fretboard',
  answer: 'name',
}

export const panel2 = {
  id: '2',
  question: 'fretboard',
  answer: 'staff',
}

export const panel3 = {
  id: '3',
  question: 'fretboard',
  answer: 'sound',
}
